<resources >
    <string name="app_name">Affirmations2</string>
    <string name="affirmation1">The smallest choices made in your daily life creates habits and lifestyles that forms process they are the ones that can make the biggest impact.</string>
    <string name="affirmation2">The beginning of habit is like an invisible thread, but every time we repeat the act we strengthen the strand, add to it another filament until it becomes a great cable and binds us irrevocably, thought and act.</string>
    <string name="affirmation3">Goethe: Only engage, and the mind grows heated. Begin it, and the work will be completed.</string>
    <string name="affirmation4">What prevents people from hitting the Redline? Someday does. Someday is a distant horizon in the theater of your mind. Someday is dangerous and paralysing. It traps you in land of Nowheresville.</string>
    <string name="affirmation5">If you retrace poverty\'s footprints you will find that poorness starts at the exact same place: choice.</string>
    <string name="affirmation6">Can you make a choice this instant that can forever alter the trajectory of your future? You can, and it can be the difference between poverty and wealth. When you make minor permutations(choice) that deviate from your initial conditions, profound effects transpire over time.</string>
    <string name="affirmation7">At some point, most of us reach a place where we\'re afraid to fail, where we instinctively avoid failure and stick only to what is placed in front of us or only what we\'re already good at. This confines us and stifles us. We can be truly successful only at something we\'re willing to fail at. If we\'re unwilling to fail, then we\'re unwilling to succeed.</string>
    <string name="affirmation8">Amateurs sit and wait for inspiration, the rest of us just get up and go to work.</string>
    <string name="affirmation9">There always risks out there that can hurt you badly, even in the seemingly safest bets, so it\'s always best to assume you\'re missing something.\nRay</string>
    <string name="affirmation10">In the final analysis, success in any area requires tons of discipline. Self-discipline, self-mastery, and self-control are the basic building blocks of character and high performance.</string>
    <string name="affirmation11">If you just observe yourself, you will see how many unnecessary movements your body is making, when you stand, sit and speak. If you look at your life and see, you will see that probably more than half the time is taken up in this. There is so much unnecessary thought and activity with the body-things that you yourself fdo not care for. But, if you keep the body still, slowly the mind starts collapsing.</string>
    <string name="affirmation12">Don\'t just sit there. Do something. The answers will follow.</string>
    <string name="affirmation13">If you are not conscious of your mortality, somewhere you think you\'re immortal. If you\'re conscious, would you have time to crib, would you gave time to fight with somebody, would you have time to do some rubbish with your life?</string>
    <string name="affirmation14">Ask for forgiveness not permission.</string>
    <string name="affirmation15">When the clubface hits the ball square, the ball goes straight and heads toward the hole. But when the clubface is rotated a fraction of one degree, the ball\'s trajectory lands far off course. At impact, the divergence is minor, but as the ball travels further is widens and widens until the gap is so large that getting back on track is nearly impossible. A bad choice can set your trajectory off by only one degree today, but over years the error is magnified. Choices have this type of divergence over time</string>
    <string name="affirmation16">You choices have significant trajectory into the future, and the younger you are, the more horsepower they exude. Unfortunately, horsepower fades with age. When you are under 25 you have maximum horsepower and your choices discharge and incredible amount firepower. A simple choice I made more than 20 years ago is still felt today. That\'s a lot of torque! If you reflect on your choices, you make them in an instant, yet their consequences transcend a lifetime, especially ones made early in life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation17">Your life\'s choices are like a mature oak tree with millions of branches. The branches symbolize the consequences of your choices. Near the trunk of the tree, the branches are thick, reflecting the decisions you\'ve made early in life, while the top branches are thin, symbolize decisions near the end of your life.</string>
    <string name="affirmation18">Listen, smile, agree, and then do whatever you were gonna do anyway.</string>
    <string name="affirmation19">Never tell your problems to everyone.80% don\'t care and the other 20% are glad you have them.</string>
    <string name="affirmation20">Fuck Friends. Go to that concert by yourself, Don\'t wait on people, Do what you want to do, Go to that park by yourself, Go eat that restaurant you keep saying you want to go, Go try those crazy shits you always wanted to try, Don\'t wait on people. And if your friends don\'t want to do it.\nDo it anyways.</string>
    <string name="affirmation21">The first lesson of car ownership: Change the oil every 3,000 miles. Neglect the lesson and your car dies well before its useful life. Frequent oil changes keep your car running efficiently, unchanged oil goes stale and turns the ride rough. Rough rides stall to the shoulder of the road. The Fastlane road trip demands fresh oil changes. But what is oil? Oil is education. Knowledge. Street smarts. But be careful… it must be the right oil and for the right purpose.</string>
    <string name="affirmation22">People the a growth mindset don\'t seek challenge, they thrive on it. The bigger the challenge the more they stretch. </string>


</resources>